tipjunkie.com 2017-10-01

# Privacy Policy, FTC Disclosure, Sweepstakes Policy | Tip Junkie

## **FTC Full Disclosure**

This blog is a collaborative blog written by a group of individuals. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

## Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions
  * Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies  and other tracking signals to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not share, sell, trade, email addresses or personal information that we collect or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.tipjunkie.com/terms-and-conditions/>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on October 21, 2013

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. http://www.tipjunkie.com/  3238 Woodstone Drive  Lewis Center, Ohio 43035  United States  contact@tipjunkie.com

## **Giveaway and Sweepstakes Policy**

This statement sets forth the terms and conditions under which a giveaway where a winner is chosen at random (Sweepstakes) are executed by Tip Junkie.

No purchase is necessary to enter any Sweepstakes on TipJunkie.com. All entrants must be U.S. residents, ages 18 years or older, and must provide a valid email address.

The odds of winning a Sweepstakes is dependent on the number of entries. Winners will be selected randomly by Tip Junkie using http://random.org as the selection tool and have 48 hours to claim their prize. If a potential Prize winner forfeits or does not claim a prize, the prize will be re-awarded, in Tip Junkie sole discretion. All prizes will be awarded.

Employees of Tip Junkie and the Sweepstakes Sponsor are not eligible to participate. All entries received after the Sweepstakes closing date and time will not be considered. Entries that do not follow all of the entry requirements will not be considered. Tip Junkie and Sweepstakes Sponsor are not liable for late or misdirected entries, entry errors, or transmission problems.

All decisions of Tip Junkie are final.

Tip Junkie reserve the right to terminate the Sweepstakes in the event of technical problems, or to correct typographical or technical errors, or to amend these rules.

By entering, participants agree to release and hold harmless Tip Junkie, Sweepstakes Sponsor, and their respective parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, directors, officers, employees, and agents from any and all liability or any injuries, loss, or damage of any kind arising from or in connection with a Sweepstakes.

All Sweepstakes winners must be willing to furnish a valid shipping address in order to receive a prize. Winners also agree to release and not to sue Tip Junkie for use of their name, logo, domain, and/or likeness including, without limitation, claims for invasion of privacy, infringement of the right of publicity, liable, unfair competition, false advertising, intentional or negligent infliction of emotional distress, and/or copyright or trademark infringement.

Taxes on Sweepstakes are solely the responsibility of the Winner.

Non-winning entries from one Sweepstakes may not be carried forward to future Sweepstakes.

All Sweepstakes are subject to and must be construed under the laws of the State of Ohio, except where prohibited by law.

*******By submitting an entry you agree to all of these terms and conditions.*******
